{
  "type": "writing",
  "language_code": "zh-CN",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "Xiūxí",
      "answer": "休息"
    },
    {
      "question": "Gěi",
      "answer": "给"
    },
    {
      "question": "Guàhào",
      "answer": "挂号"
    },
    {
      "question": "Yǒudiǎn er",
      "answer": "有点儿"
    },
    {
      "question": "Fāyán",
      "answer": "发炎"
    },
    {
      "question": "Fāshāo",
      "answer": "发烧"
    },
    {
      "question": "Gǎnmào",
      "answer": "感冒"
    },
    {
      "question": "Zhùyuàn",
      "answer": "住院"
    },
    {
      "question": "Shuǐ",
      "answer": "水"
    },
    {
      "question": "Yào",
      "answer": "药"
    },
    {
      "question": "Yuànyì",
      "answer": "愿意"
    },
    {
      "question": "Zhōngyào",
      "answer": "中药"
    },
    {
      "question": "Xīyào",
      "answer": "西药"
    }
  ]
}
